usocial.net 2011-12-30

# uSocial - Privacy Policy

We at uSocial.net take the privacy and security of our users very seriously. Please make sure you read and understand fully your rights and responsibilities when using our Site and Services.

 **1\. What This Policy Covers**  
This policy covers all the Services provided by uSocial as laid out in the Terms. In any case where more detailed information is needed to further explain our privacy policies, we ask that you do not hesitate to contact us.

 **2\. Information You Provide**  
In the event that you sign up for any kind of uSocial account, or other uSocial service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our advertising programs, we may also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers which are operated by third parties such as 2Checkout.com. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other uSocial services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services, however we will never share this information with any outside or unauthorised party. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.

**3\. Cookies**  
When you visit uSocial, we may at any point send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters which is loaded onto your computer – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. uSocial may also use cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set a cookie in your browser when you visit a website and view or click on an ad supported by uSocial's advertising services.

**4\. Information Recording**  
When you access uSocial Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.  

**5\. User Communication**  
When you send email or other communications to uSocial, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**6\. Affiliated Websites**  
We may offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to uSocial in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

**7\. Links**  
uSocial may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customised content and advertising.

**8\. Other Websites**  
This Privacy Policy applies to uSocial services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

**9\. Collection**  
uSocial only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

> **a.** Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising; **b.** Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; **c.** Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and **d.** Developing new services.

uSocial processes personal information on servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising and affiliated partners.

**10\. Sharing of Information**  
uSocial only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of uSocial in the following limited circumstances:  

> **a.** We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. **b.** We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. **c.** We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of uSocial, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If uSocial becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Please contact us for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

**11\. Security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to personal information to uSocial employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**12\. Integrity**  
uSocial processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.  

**13\. Information Updating**  
When you use uSocial services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information.

**14\. Enforcement**  
uSocial regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or uSocial’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this website. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is uSocial’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between uSocial and an individual. 

**15\. Changes**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). If you have any other questions or concerns regarding any part of this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us through this website..
